Finding Aid for John and Leni Sinclair Papers 1957-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Textual Records
  - Rainbow Productions, Inc.
    - Detroit Church of Life (Box 16)
    - Detroit Blues Club (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Proposals (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Strata Corporation/Strata Associates Inc.
    - Correspondence and agreements (Box 16)
    - Board of Directors minutes and organizational papers (Box 16)
    - Press releases (Box 16)
    - Articles (Box 16)
    - Allied Artists Association of America, Inc.
      - Press releases, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Flyers, programs and miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Contemporary Jazz Quintet (Box 16)
    - Lyman Woodard Organization (Box 17)
    - Flyers (Box 17)
    - Graphics (Box 17)
    - Strata Records (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Sun newspaper
    (variously called Warren-Forest Sun, Sun/Dance, Ann Arbor Sun, The Detroit Sun)
    - Correspondence, staff meeting notes and reports (Box 17)
    - Financial, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Sun history and press releases (Box 17)
    - Flyers and note cards (Box 17)
    - Graphics (Box 17)
    - Free Suns, street sheets, and Suns from other cities (Box 17)
    - Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - White Panther Party / Youth International Party
    - Correspondence and financial (Box 17)
    - Minutes
      - Central Committee July 1970-April 1971 (Box 17)
      - House meetings circa May 1970-April 1971 (Box 17)
    - Ideology
      - Organization, history and program (Box 17)
      - Media guide, reading lists and course outlines (Box 17)
      - Reports and proposals to the Central Committee (Box 17)
      - Statements and miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Press releases
      - Undated (Box 17)
      - 1969 (Box 17)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 17)
    - Flyers (Box 17)
    - Party chapters outside Ann Arbor (Box 17)
    - Black Panthers/Red Star Conspiracies, Inc./Woodstock People's Party (Box 17)
    - Sheriff Harvey Recall Campaign (Box 17)
    - Clippings re. WPP/RPP, 4 folders (Box 17)
    - Clippings re. WPP/RPP, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Rainbow People's Party
    - Minutes
      - Central Committee
        - May-November 1971 (Box 18)
        - April-August 1972 (Box 18)
        - September-December 1972 (Box 18)
        - 1973 (Box 18)
      - Party meetings 1972-1973 (Box 18)
      - Cadre meetings 1973 (Box 18)
      - House meetings May 1971-July 1972 (Box 18)
    - Ideology-organization, history, program, statements and correspondence (Box 18)
    - Press releases (Box 18)
    - American Radical Media Group/New Morning (Box 18)
    - Indo-China Medicine Show (Box 18)
    - Legal Defense Fund (Box 18)
    - Friends of the Rainbow People/Rainbow Students' Union/Students for Human Rights (Box 18)
    - Crater movement, house operation and miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Human Rights Party
    - General, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - David Sinclair campaign for Ann Arbor City council 1973 (Box 18)
    - Clippings (Box 18)
  - Tribal Council
    - Ann Arbor
      - General (Box 18)
      - Children's Community Center (Box 18)
      - Community Park Program (free concerts) (Box 18)
      - People's Ballroom
        - General (Box 18)
        - Agreements (Box 18)
      - Tribal Funding, Inc.
        - Legal-corporation papers, agreements and litigation (Box 18)
        - Correspondence, financial and miscellaneous (Box 18)
      - WNRZ (Box 18)
      - Flyers (Box 18)
      - Clippings (Box 18)
    - Detroit
      - People's Ballroom (Box 18)
      - Rock and Roll News (Box 18)
  - Legal and Prison Files
    - People of the State of Mich. vs. John A. Sinclair (Marijuana case)
      - Detroit Recorder's Court
        - A-134588 Motion to Quash Information, Brief and Opinions October 1967-1968 (Box 19)
        - A-134588 Brief to Support Information November 15, 1967 (Box 19)
          (printed by AWS w/Stringfellow poem and JS biography)
        - A-134588 Transcript, July 22, June 24 July 24, 1969 (Box 19)
        - A-134588 Sentencing July 28, 1969 and Criminal Record (Box 19)
      - State Court of Appeals
        - Emergency application for appeal bond July 28, 1969 (Box 19)
        - 5194 Brief for Defendant-Appellant February 4, 1970 (Box 19)
        - 5194 Excerpts from brief for defendant-appellant (Box 19)
        - 7814 Docs February-April 1971 (Box 19)
      - State Supreme Court
        - 53550 Brief in support of application for leave to appeal July, 1971 (Box 19)
        - 53550 Briefs and court orders July 27-October 28, 1971 (Box 19)
        - 53550 Opinions October 19, 1971 and Order for release, December 13, 1971 (Box 19)
      - U.S. District Court
        - 37502 Docs December 1971 (Box 19)
    - People of State of Mich. vs. John Alexander Sinclair and Frederick Dewey Smith (Oakland Co. Assault case)
      - Justice Court for Township of Waterford
        - CR 68-4146 Transcript September 12, 1968, October 10, 1968 (Box 19)
        - CR 68-4146 Sinclair's Statement January 20, 1969 and Transcript-printed (Box 19)
        - CR 68-4146 Miscellaneous (Box 19)
      - Oakland County Circuit Court
        - CR 68-4146 Motion for New Trial-Transcript June 10, 1969 (Box 19)
      - State Court of Appeals
        - 7822 Brief on Appeal June 30, 1970 and Dismissal, March 1971 (Box 19)
    - United States of America vs. John Sinclair, Lawrence Robert, Pun Plamondon and John Waterhouse Forrest (CIA case)
      - 44375 Docs October 1969-October 1970 (Box 19)
      - 44375 Docs October 9-10, 1970 (Box 19)
      - 44375 Docs October 16-December 23, 1970 (Box 19)
      - 44375 Opinions January 1971 (Box 19)
      - 3805 Related docs from United States vs. Milton Edward Taube and John Waterhouse Forrest 1972 (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous Taube, Plamondon, and Forrest legal documents (Box 19)
    - John Sinclair vs. George Kropp
      - 34609 and 20485 Docs March-June 1970 (Box 19)
    - John Sinclair vs. Perry Johnson
      - 35674 Docs 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - John Sinclair vs. Perry Johnson and Gus Harrison
      (1983 suit or Jackson Prison suit)
      - 35809 Docs December 1970-April 1971 (Box 19)
      - 35809 Docs August 1971, October 1971 (Box 19)
      - 35809 Interrogatories October 1971 (Box 19)
    - John Sinclair, et al. vs. Richard G. Kleindienst, et al.
      - 610-73 Docs 1973-1974, 1976, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Materials
      - 1964-1970, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - People of the State of Michigan vs. Craig Brazier and Lawrence R. (Pun) Plamondon (Box 20)
      - CIA Conspiracy Trial 1971, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Notes (Box 20)
      - Prison regulations, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Visitor record, block reports and disciplinary board reports (Box 20)
      - Correspondence file kept by State Prison of Southern Michigan (Box 20)
      - Indexed Prison file #1, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Indexed Prison file #2 (Box 20)
      - Unindexed Prison file
        - 1969-1970 (Box 20)
        - 1971 (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous Prison memos, receipts, etc. (Box 20)
      - Prison newspapers (Box 20)
      - Justice for Americans Imprisoned and Lost (J.A.I.L.) (Box 20)
      - Prison reform (Box 20)
      - Wayne County Jail miscellanea (Box 20)
      - David Sinclair legal miscellanea (Box 20)
      - Michigan Committee for Prisoners' Rights (MCPR)
        - Corporation papers, correspondence and press releases (Box 20)
        - Prisoners' Labor Union (Box 20)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Lawsuits and trials 1978-1999
      - John Sinclair, et al. v. Richard Kleindeinst, et al. 1978-1990 (Box 20)
      - Wiretap press articles 1983 (Box 20)
      - John Sinclair v. Detroit Free Press 1986-1989, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - John Sinclair v. City of Detroit
        - Various Briefs and documents 1991-1992 (Box 20)
        - Depositions 1991 (Box 20)
      - John Sinclair, Lawrence Plamondon, John W. Forrest, v. Kenneth Schriber, James Sullivan, and Charles Wagner, (CIA Wire Tap, civil law suit)
        - Correspondence 1985-1990 (Box 20)
        - David Sinclair, notes and correspondence 1986-1989 (Box 20)
          (includes notes/logs on wiretap tape recordings)
        - Motions filed 1989 (Box 20)
    - Divorce papers and miscellaneous legal documents 1987-1988 (Box 46)
    - Red squad and police files
      - Michigan state police files, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Detroit police files, 1966-1970 (Box 46)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) documents
      - FOIA correspondence,1975-1977 (Box 46)
      - FOIA FBI documents, 1969-1974 (Box 46)
  - Free John Now Campaign
    - Press releases, flyers and other publicity material
      - John Sinclair Defense Fund/White Panther Party (Box 46)
      - Committee to Free John Sinclair (Box 46)
      - Other (Box 46)
    - "Ten for Two: The John Sinclair Freedom Rally"-A Joko film
      - Correspondence (Box 46)
      - Press releases, clippings and miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - "The Entrapment of John Sinclair" by Ed Sanders (Box 46)
    - Benefit posters (Box 46)
    - Sun supplements and rally program (Box 46)
    - Clippings (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
  - Marijuana Reform
    - Lemar
      - Detroit (Box 46)
      - New York State (Box 46)
      - San Francisco (Box 46)
    - Amorphia: The Cannabis Cooperative
      - Board of Directors-minutes, memos and financial, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 21)
      - The Amorphia Report and press releases (Box 21)
      - The Marijuana Review (Box 21)
      - Articles, reports, and legal (Box 21)
      - Promotional material (Box 21)
      - Clippings and reprints (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - California Marijuana Initiative (CMI)
      - Correspondence, legal and miscellaneous (Box 21)
      - Press releases (Box 21)
      - Grass Roots Gazette (Box 21)
      - Proposition 19 Speakers' Handbook (Box 21)
      - Promotional material (Box 21)
      - Clippings (Box 21)
    - Michigan Marijuana Initiative (MMI)
      - Correspondence and proposed legislation (Box 21)
      - Press releases and Marijuana Revolution by John Sinclair (Box 21)
      - Promotional and miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws (NORML)
      - Michigan (Box 21)
      - Washington, D.C. (Box 21)
    - Marijuana Information Transfer-report and news releases (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 8 folders (Box 21)
  - Writings
    - Pre-1978
      - Flint College student essays and publications, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Wayne State Univ. student publications 1962-1963 (Box 21)
      - Master's Thesis 1966 (Box 21)
      - Published writings, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Manuscripts
        - Political, 6 folders (Box 22)
        - Re. arrest and imprisonment (Box 22)
        - Music, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - "Prison Diary": poetry, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - "Dragon Teeth", 2 folders (Box 22)
        - "Rainbow Bridge" (Box 22)
        - Detroit history and development piece, notes 1977 (Box 22)
        - Plays/sketches ("A Christmas Carol," "The Square") (Box 22)
        - Writing Projects index 1977 (Box 22)
      - Periodical and newspaper articles
        - "The Coatpuller" published in The Fifth Estate, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - "Rock and Roll Dope" published in The Fifth Estate (Box 22)
        - "R and R Crusader" published in The Fifth Estate (Box 22)
        - Fifth Estate articles (Box 22)
        - Record reviews (Box 22)
        - Ann Arbor Argus articles (Box 22)
        - Ann Arbor Sun articles (Box 22)
        - Creem articles (Box 22)
        - Book reviews, miscellaneous articles, and announcements of readings (Box 22)
      - Poetry
        - John Sinclair (Box 22)
        - "Book of Love," 1977 (Box 22)
        - "Bridgework," various dates 1960s (Box 22)
        - "The Leni Poems," various dates 1960s (Box 22)
        - "Smoking Bananas" (Box 22)
        - Various 1964-1978, 8 folders (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Leni Sinclair (Box 23)
        - Drafts and fragments, 4 folders (Box 23)
        - Written by others/unidentified, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Guitar Army, published copy, drafts, deletions, and related matter (Box 23)
        (unprocessed)
      - Artists Workshop notebooks, desk calendars, address books, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Prison notebooks, notepads, and diary (Box 23)
      - Prison notebooks, notepads, and diary (cont.) (Box 24)
    - Writings 1978-1999
      - Poetry
        - "Blow Baby, Blow: Collected Poems," 1996, 2 folders (Box 47)
        - "Eddie Jefferson Said," 1991 (Box 47)
        - "'Evidence-(Penny's Book)" 1988 (Box 47)
        - "'Fattening Frogs For Snakes'-Delta Sound Suite"
          - Various Drafts and revisions 1987-1995, 5 folders (Box 47)
          - Visuals (Box 47)
          - Index (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and Miscellaneous (Box 47)
        - "Full Circle: Selected Poems," 1997 (Box 47)
        - "Thelonius: A Book of Monk"/"Rhythym-a-ning: A Book of Monk"
          - Various Drafts and revisions 1985-1996, 11 folders (Box 47)
          - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 47)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 47)
        - "Fly Right: A Monk Suite," 1991, 1996, 2 folders (Box 47)
        - "I Mean You: A Book for Penny," Various Drafts and revisions 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 47)
        - "Songs of Praise: Homage to John Coltrane," Various Drafts and revisions 1988-1996, 3 folders (Box 48)
        - "The Sweet Suite," 1978 (Box 48)
        - "Viper Mad Suite," 1998, 2 folders (Box 48)
        - "We Just Change the Beat: Selected Poems", published version, revisions, reviews, and promotional 1988 (Box 48)
        - Miscellaneous Poetry files 1978-1995, 9 folders (Box 48)
      - Periodical and newspaper articles/features
        - Mitch Ryder article Detroit Free Press, 1983 (Box 48)
        - Entertainment Revue article (Box 48)
        - "Artist Calling," Detroit Free Press, 1984 (Box 48)
        - Mardi Gras Indians article City Arts Quarterly, 1987 (Box 48)
        - "What Makes San Francisco Great," 1988 (Box 48)
        - "Turn on Your Volume Baby: WWOZ and the Sound of New Orleans," 1988 (Box 48)
        - "Ancient to the Future: The Art Ensemble of Chicago," Detroit Free Press, 1988 (Box 48)
        - "By the Time We Got to Woodstock," Detroit Free Press, 1988 (Box 48)
        - "A Strange and Celestial Road: Sun Ra and his Outer Space Music," Detroit Free Press, 1988 (Box 48)
        - 'The Original Chess Masters," 1988 (Box 48)
        - "Robert Jr. Lockwood: Blues from the Delta," Detroit Free Press, 1988 (Box 48)
        - "The Sun Messengers," 1989 (Box 48)
        - "The Devil's Music," (Playboy history of Jazz and Rock, Part I)
          - Published article (Box 48)
          - Research and drafts (Box 48)
          - Correspondence (Box 48)
        - Playboy history of Jazz and Rock, Part II (unpublished) (Box 48)
        - Michael McClure and Ray Manzarek: Poet and Pianist open the Doors of Perception," Detroit Free Press, 1989 (Box 48)
        - "Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival, 1992" Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz program supplement (Box 48)
        - "Howls, Raps, and Roars: A celebration of Beat Poetry," Detroit Free Press, 1993 (Box 48)
        - "Jazz loses a True Innovator in Sun Ra," Lagniappe, 1993 (Box 48)
        - "A Joyful Noise: The Music of New Orleans," Cutting Edge Music Festival Program 1993 (Box 48)
        - "Notes from the Cutting Edge," Cutting Edge Music Festival Program 1993 (Box 48)
        - "On the Cutting Edge," Cutting Edge Music Festival Program 1994 (Box 48)
        - "Neushi Ertegun," 37th Annual Grammy Awards Program 1995 (Box 48)
        - "Homage to Snooks Eaglin," Offbeat, 1995 (Box 48)
        - "The Wild Indians of Mardi Gras," Inside New Orleans, 1995 (Box 48)
        - Jazz Fest 1996 writings, Where magazine, 1996 (Box 48)
        - "New Orleans Nightcrawlers," 1996 (Box 48)
        - "Travel/New Orleans," 1997 (Box 48)
        - "Ten Spots," 1997 (Box 48)
        - "Robert Palmer: An Appreciation," Offbeat, 1997 (Box 48)
        - "New Orleans the Birth Place of Jazz," Markets, 1998 (Box 48)
        - "The Deep South," (for Music of the World Festival) 1998 (Box 48)
        - "Introduction: Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival, 1972 to 1974" Blues Access, 1998 (Box 48)
        - "'Viper Mad: The 11th Annual Cannabis Cup," High Times, 1998 (Box 48)
        - "T-Model Ford," 1998 (Box 48)
      - Interviews
        - Dave Bartholomew 1982 (Box 49)
        - Dr. John/Martin Gross 1989 (Box 49)
        - Tyree Guyton 1989 (Box 49)
        - Ron Milner 1989 (Box 49)
        - Rebennak, Mac 1982 (Box 49)
        - Robbie Robertson Wavelength, 1991 (Box 49)
        - Roland Stone Offbeat, 1993 (Box 49)
        - Johnny Adams Offbeat, 1993 (Box 49)
        - Robert Palmer Offbeat, 1994 (Box 49)
        - Dr. John Offbeat, 1994 (Box 49)
        - Harold Battiste Offbeat, 1994 (Box 49)
        - Michael Ray Offbeat, 1994 (Box 49)
        - Coco Robicheaux Offbeat, 1995 (Box 49)
        - Chuck Carbo, Eddie Bo, Deacon John Offbeat, 1996 (Box 49)
        - Ernie K-Doe Offbeat, 1996 (Box 49)
        - Kevin Clark 1996 (Box 49)
        - Walter "Wolfman" Washington 1996 (Box 49)
        - Carlo Ditta 1998 (Box 49)
        - Johnnie Basset 1999 (Box 49)
        - Coco Robicheaux 1999 (Box 49)
      - Liner notes
        - Peter "Madcat" Ruth Madcat's Pressure Cooker, 1988 (Box 49)
        - Billy C. Farlow, "Too Much Fun," 1991 (Box 49)
        - Leo Smith, "Kulture Jazz," 1993 (Box 49)
        - Solomon Burke, "Soul of the Blues," 1993 (Box 49)
        - Kiss me Screaming 1993 (Box 49)
        - Mustang Lightning 1993 (Box 49)
        - Bob Moses, "Time Stood Still," 1993 (Box 49)
        - Brass Construction 1993 (Box 49)
        - Dennis Formento 1993 (Box 49)
        - Parliament ("My favorite P-Funk memory") 1994 (Box 49)
        - Michael Ray and the Cosmic Crewe 1994 (Box 49)
        - The Isley Brothers, "Beautiful Ballads," 1994 (Box 49)
        - Rebirth Brass Band, "Rollin'" 1994 (Box 49)
        - The Adams-Griffin Project, "the Sound of New Orleans Records," 1994 (Box 49)
        - Coco Robicheaux, "Spiritland," 1994 (Box 49)
        - High Street Rhythm Rockers, "As Blues as it Gets," 1994 (Box 49)
        - "The Sound of New Orleans, Volume 2" (WWOZ) 1994 (Box 49)
        - "Please Mr. Foreman: Motor City Blues" (Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1973), 1994 (Box 49)
        - Johnny Adams 1994 (Box 49)
        - "If You Don't Know Me by Now: The Best of Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes," 1994 (Box 49)
        - The Rationals, "'Live' at the Grande Ballroom," 1995 (Box 49)
        - John Sinclair and Ed Moss, "If I could Be with You," 1995 (Box 49)
        - "Grind It," (Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1973, Volume 3) 1995 (Box 49)
        - "Well All Right," Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1973, Vol. 3 1996 (Box 49)
        - Timothea, "Goin' Home to Mama," 1996 (Box 49)
        - Rockin' Jake Band, "Let's go Get 'em," 1996 (Box 49)
        - MC 5, "Starship: Live at the Sturgis Armory, 1968" 1998 (Box 49)
        - Wild Magnolias, "Life is a Carnival," 1998 (Box 49)
        - "Motor City Blues," (Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1973), 1998 (Box 49)
        - Davell Crawford, "Born with the Funk," 1999 (Box 49)
        - Sun Ra, "Outer Space Employment Agency" (Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz festival 1973), 1999 (Box 49)
        - Robert Parker, "Bare Footin'" 1999 (Box 49)
        - Stavin' Chain 1999 (Box 49)
      - Reviews
        - Detroit News jazz reviews, 1982 (Box 49)
        - The Art of Rock book review, 1987 (Box 49)
        - The Lives of John Lennon (Albert Goldman) book review, 1988 (Box 49)
        - Guitar Slim/Kenny Neal review 1988 (Box 49)
        - The Wild One (Iggy Pop) book review, 1989 (Box 49)
        - The Neville Brothers Yellow Moon Rising, 1989 (Box 49)
        - Ed Sanders Tales of Beatnik Glory-Vols. One and Two, Book review, 1991 (Box 49)
        - Jack Kerouac Pomes All Sizes, book review, 1992 (Box 49)
        - Howls Raps and Roars: Recordings from the San Francisco Poetry Renaissance, 1993 (Box 49)
        - Fess- The Professor Long Hair Anthology, 1993 (Box 49)
        - Offbeat magazine Reviews, 1994 (Box 49)
        - Chuck Carbo Barber's Blues, 1995 (Box 49)
        - John Coltrane The Heavyweight Champion: The Complete Atlantic Recordings, 1995 (Box 49)
        - Tommy Ridgely Since the Blues Began, 1995 (Box 49)
        - Rebirth Brass Band We Come to Party, 1997 (Box 49)
        - Root Doctor The Doctor is In, 1997 (Box 49)
        - Wayne Kramer Citizen Wayne, 1997 (Box 49)
        - William Burroughs Word Virus: The William S. Burroughs Reader book review, 1999 (Box 49)
        - Hasting Street Grease: Detroit Blues is Alive, Volume 2, 1999 (Box 49)
      - Columns
        - "'Sides," City of San Francisco 1976 (Box 49)
        - "Roots and Branches," 1978 (Box 49)
        - "Coat Puller," Detroit Music Times 1981 (Box 49)
        - "Blues and Roots," 1991 (Box 49)
        - "Crescent City Bounce," Offbeat 1993-1995 (Box 49)
        - "Kulture," no date (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Poetry of Rhythm and Blues 1981 (Box 49)
        - Music Hound Artist Biographies 1997 (Box 49)
        - Fragments and Miscellaneous 1981 (Box 49)
        - "Passing it On," manuscript 1970s (Box 49)
        - Notebooks, diaries and workbooks, scattered dates (Box 50)
  - Personal-Early Years
    - Sinclair baby book (Box 50)
    - Personal, school, family materials, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - David Sinclair writings, clippings, and high school miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Kathleen Sinclair miscellaneous (Box 50)
    - Davison High School yearbooks, 3 volumes (Box 50)
    - Albion College yearbook 1960 (Box 50)
  - Topical File
    - Pre-1978
      - The Alternative Press, Detroit/Grindstone City Poems, broadsides, postcards (Box 25)
      - Communication Company, UPS (Box 25)
      - The Red Hanrahan Press/Highland Park Poems 1972-1973 (Box 25)
      - Rock and Roll Cooperative DFM Local 5 Minutes February 19, 1968 (Box 25)
      - Sports Consultants, Inc. 1974 (Box 25)
      - Youth Liberation (Box 25)
      - Miscellanea, 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous business cards and buttons (Box 25)
    - 1978-1999
      - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1998 (Box 25)
      - Artist's Workshop Reunion (Box 25)
      - Beatlecon 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Big Easy Awards 1995 (Box 25)
      - Blues Access Magazine 1999 (Box 25)
      - Blues Hall of Fame/Blues Foundation 1995 (Box 25)
      - Bluestock 1998 (Box 25)
      - Caddy Awards 1978 (Box 25)
      - Cannabis Cup 1998 (Box 25)
      - City Arts Quarterly 1989-1990 (Box 25)
      - Composers Concept, Jazz at the Paradise 1978 (Box 25)
      - Crescent City Blues Club 1994 (Box 25)
      - Cuba Trip 1996 (Box 25)
      - Cutting Edge Music Conference 1993, 1996-1998, 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Davison High school, 30th reunion 1989 (Box 25)
      - Delta Blues Cruise 1989 (Box 25)
      - Detroit Council for the Arts 1988 (Box 25)
      - Detroit Institute for the Arts-"Artist's Call," 1990 (Box 25)
      - Detroit Jazz Center 1979, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Discographical Research 1980s, 1990s (scattered dates), 4 folders (Box 25)
        (Research on various blues/jazz/R&B recording artists and record labels)
      - Financial documents, Scattered dates (Box 25)
      - Grant applications 1989-1999, 7 folders (Box 25)
      - "The Great Debate," (television show) 1978 (Box 25)
      - Handy Awards 1995 (Box 25)
      - Human Rights Festival, Atlanta, GA 1998 (Box 25)
      - "I Rip You, You Rip Me," (Exhibition on Detroit Rock and Roll, Rotterdam, the Netherlands) 1998 (Box 25)
      - Jazz For Life Project 1987 (Box 51)
      - Jazz Research Institute 1979 (Box 51)